[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I ran from my bathroom into the kitchen where I decided to eat breakfast to calm my nerves. Unfortunately, my aichmophobia was provoked when I opened the silverware drawer. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Pointed objects", "incorrect_answers": ["Spiders", "Rattling sounds", "Crumbs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?", "correct_answer": "8,849 m", "incorrect_answers": ["8,859 m", "8,850 m", "8,840 m"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of Cheechs cousin, Duane Mendoza, who parties all night with Chong in Cheech and Chongs Next Movie?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Fred", "Jose", "Pedro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pure water, if it exists, has this pH.", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "14", "0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What period marked the popularity of the cloche hat?", "correct_answer": "1920s", "incorrect_answers": ["1970s", "18th century", "15t century"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the smallest species of deer in the world, found only in South America?", "correct_answer": "Northern Pudu", "incorrect_answers": ["Marsh Deer", "Southern Pudu", "Antifer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With its vivid references to death, It would be hard to find a song more dark and haunting than the tune featured in the audio clip.  Which group recorded this hit back in 1976?", "correct_answer": "Blue \u00d6yster Cult", "incorrect_answers": ["Santana", "Steely Dan", "Foghat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city, situated on the River Vltava, is sometimes called the mother of cities, the city of a hundred spires and the golden city.", "correct_answer": "Prague", "incorrect_answers": ["Athens", "Rome", "Bucharest"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potatoes contain toxic chemicals that are also found in tobacco and tomatoes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following dialogue is from the movie Star Trek IV - The Voyage Home.   \nKirk: Oh, him? (referring to Spock ) I think he did a little too much LDS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie WALL-E, the Captain disables the Auto Pilot by ordering him to give him control.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hexagon ABCDEF has six equal sides and six equal angles. How many degrees is each angle?", "correct_answer": "120 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["144 degrees", "90 degrees", "180 degrees"]}]